This is O'Hare, California.
Back then, it was nothing more
than a sleepy fishing village
with a hill at the end
of Main Street.
Like you see
in postcards.
- My story takes place
on the home front,
in the midst
of World War II.
That's me...
the little fella.
Closer?
Stop causing trouble,
you midget.
Nobody in that town
liked me much.
One, two, three.
I was eight years old.
But the story really starts
the day I met my dad.
My only friend.
My partner.
- He's a boy.
- Wow.
- He's so...
- What? Little?
Well, he'll grow.
Right?
I got you covered, okay?
'Cause we're partners.
I wanted to be
just like him.
And do everything
he did.
And everything we did
became a great adventure.
Very proud
of you, partner.
You handled the pain
like a true hero.
Actually, you remind me
of another hero...
"Ben Eagle,
The Magician. "
Ben Eagle said to his sidekick,
"Do you believe you can do this?"
"Do you believe
you can do this?"
That became our motto.
- Do you believe we can do this?
- Yes, I believe we can do this.
Let's go, partner.
The mast is broken.
Partner, do you believe
you can do this?
Yes, I believe
I can do this.
This is the police.
Partner, do you believe
we can do this?
Yes, partner.
Pepper.
Pepper Flynt Busbee,
I've been yelling
for 20 minutes.
That's my mom.
Come on, we're in the
middle of a great story.
Always there to snap us
back to reality.
It's time to go to bed.
Come on.
And that's my brother,
London.
Finally old enough to sign up
for the fight.
- Bye, Mom. - All was
good in the old Busbee home.
Or so I thought.
The new "Ben Eagle"!
You gotta bring your quarter
for a look-see.
- What are you having, your usual today?
- Yeah, give me the usual.
Me too.
The war was still raging.
The enemy has
infiltrated the USA.
Stupid American,
you know not what Tokyo do.
Not on my watch,
little fella.
Everyone was pitching in,
doing their part.
Uncle Sam had all
the teens lining up,
ready to fight.
Busbee, London.
Sorry, son.
4F.
Hoffman, William.
Sergeant, sir?
With all due respect,
what do flat feet have
to do with killing Japs?
That's just
the way it is, kid.
Thanks.
Welcome to the US Army.
Landry, Gene.
How's the weather
down there, "Midget"?
Two vanillas.
Hey, the world looks bigger
from down here.
He sure is small.
Hey, where's your cane,
"Tiny Tim"?
You think you're gonna
buy 'em this time?
No, not today.
Piece of junk!
4F.
Stupid war.
I can't let you do this, Dad.
This is my fight.
But you always knew
one of us had to go.
It was supposed
to be me.
Come on, Lon. Aren't you
gonna eat anything?
London's not going to war,
right?
Does that mean that...
you're going instead?
Yes.
He'll be back
before you know it.
Why can't we
stay together?
Partner,
I have to go.
I don't want you to go.
Time's up, privates.
You have nothing
to blame yourself about.
- You take care of yourself, okay?
- All right.
I'm not
a midget, right?
We shouldn't
use that word.
"Midget" is a mean word
for people with dwarfism.
I'm afraid your son had something
to do with the nickname.
- Mom!
- That's okay, Pepper.
I will make sure Freddy
makes things right.
Any news from James?
He should be here on the 15th. He said
his tour would end by summer.
That's what he said
in his last letter.
Do I have dwarfism
or what?
You know what?
Let's just keep an eye on you.
You know, it's really too soon
to make any type of diagnosis.
I will, however,
suggest
we see each other
regularly.
But for now, Pepper,
let's just say you're a...
little boy.
Teacup!
Come on, get up.
Mr. Jones yelled
at me yesterday.
He really blew a fuse
about his car.
He said you were a...
- You want to know what
he called you? - No, I don't.
Let's hear this baby hum.
Why is this thing
not working?
The old one works fine.
Your dad was happy with it.
What do you know?
He's gonna love this.
Now mind your own and get
the lousy Packard ready.
- Can I go?
- Yeah, go.
Don't need your
pestering, either.
- And what about my money?
- I don't have any.
- But mom told you.
- "But mom told you. "
This ain't time to be
spending money like that.
What a waste.
Dad's been eyeing these boots
for a long time, hasn't he?
Yes, he has.
Thank you.
Hi, Jenny. Can I have two tickets
for the "Ben Eagle Show"?
Does this mean your
father's coming back?
Yeah, he should be here soon.
Bye, Jenny. Thank you.
Good morning, Mrs. Busbee.
On March 11th,
your husband,
James L. Busbee
was part of
a tactical operation.
His platoon was sent
to secure Malabang,
a village
in the Philippines.
I can't wait to see him.
He's the best.
Hey, look. It's the midget
who ratted on me.
- Come on, let's get him!
- Get him!
Fight!
Midget!
Midget! Midget!
Stop!
We can't call him "midget. "
It could traumatize him.
Gimme that.
In the name of the
freakiest thing alive,
I baptize you,
"Little Boy. "
Okay.
Is my husband
dead or alive?
We don't know, ma'am.
His body wasn't located at the scene.
We believe he's been taken
as a prisoner of war.
Good luck getting out.
What's wrong?
He's barely eaten
all week.
Just take him,
would you?
He got the extra ticket
for your dad.
Fine.
Elegant in his top hat
and floating cane,
Ben Eagle, the magician...
...is in reality...
a super crime fighter!
In today's episode,
is Tyra finally safe
from the clutches of Sir Pent?
Hey!
Going for a drink.
But the live show
is next.
This is what happens
to Ben Eagle's
precious interest.
You'll never get
away with it.
What are we gonna do?
There are too many.
Interpretation,
Kid Falcon.
I hope this works.
Ben Eagle!
And now,
the moment of truth.
I am searching.
Searching for the one who
the High Lama of Tibet told me
would be
in this very room.
The chosen one.
Me!
You.
Look who's here.
London.
My boy.
- Hey, Sam.
- Hey, London. The usual?
What you are about to see
is not an illusion.
You will bear witness
to a profound experience.
The movement
of an inanimate object
through inner power.
But I'm not gonna perform it.
My new colleague will.
Now you have the power.
It's up to you
to achieve the impossible.
But they're gonna
make fun of me.
Not if you move the bottle,
they won't. You just do as I say.
Raise your hands and
point them at the bottle.
There.
Get off the stage, runt!
Ignore the world.
- Focus.
- Stand up, little boy.
- He is standing.
- Get him a step stool.
Do you believe
you can do this?
Partner, do you believe
Do you believe you
can move it, yes or no?
Yes, I believe
I can move the bottle.
- I don't believe you.
- Yes, I believe I can move it!
- Louder.
- Yes! I can move the bottle!
That's the kind of faith
that Moses had
when he parted
the Red Sea...
the kind of faith that
little David had
when he defeated Goliath
with a little stone.
That's what we need,
my friends, in these difficult times.
So like Father Oliver
used to ask,
"What can we do?
What can we do
for our relatives at war?
if we are here
and they are there?
And the answer is...
if we have faith the size
of a mustard seed,
we can move a mountain.
If we can move
a mountain,
then nothing will be
impossible for us.
Not even ending this war
and having
our loved ones back.
I already knew someone
who could move a mountain.
I wondered if the source
of his powers
was the mustard seed.
This was a source
of unlimited powers?
So if this was true,
this was all I needed to...
And there he was...
the enemy.
- London!
- What?
There's a Jap at Gilliam's.
I couldn't understand how
one of them was free in O'Hare.
After Pearl Harbor,
they put them all in camps.
After years of internment,
the Army, in its wisdom,
has decided to release
those of Japanese ancestry
who have proven loyal
to the US.
They seem harmless, don't they?
But can we trust them?
Well, I for one,
remember Pearl Harbor,
so I say,
"Remain vigilant. "
Store doesn't serve Japs.
Everything okay here?
You forgot the onions,
Hashimoto.
- Put these on my tab.
- Father, with all due respect...
Now, Gilliam.
- These too.
- Of course, Father.
I'm getting sick and tired of hearing
again and again and again
about Pearl Harbor and about how my
son "gave his life for his country. "
Because he didn't.
Those Japs took his life.
And they did it in the most
cowardly way you can imagine.
We need to do something
about that Jap.
If I could, I would smash
every Jap with my bare hands.
That's the rat's dump.
You want to smash him
with your bare hands, huh?
Here you go.
Have at him.
Go on.
There he is!
Take that, dirty Jap!
Maybe this'll
let him know
that "slants"
ain't welcome...
I finally understood
why they don't let flat feet
into the Army.
Five groups of 10 "Hail Marys"
and five "Our Fathers. "
In Latin.
Amen.
Now you.
In Latin?
Thank God nothing
happened to Hashimoto.
- I've finished.
- Very good.
Something else?
The seed itself
doesn't do anything.
What I said is,
"If you have faith,
- the invisible power"...
- Like Ben Eagle's powers?
"Ben Eagle"?
Well, no,
that's just fantasy.
How can you say that?
I met Ben Eagle
and he showed me
how to move a bottle.
He can also move a mountain,
just like you said.
No, no, no.
That's not the same thing.
That's not faith.
Let's see.
If you have faith,
"fides" in Latin...
Crispin,
I'll take it from here.
I understand.
Take a seat.
Why don't you show me
how you moved the bottle?
- You want to see?
- Yes, I do.
I guess that
was stupid of me.
Why don't you try again?
Again.
There, it moved.
No, you moved it.
Yes, because you moved
me to move it.
See, I moved it because
you wanted the bottle
to move so much.
And that, you could say,
is how faith works.
At least some of the time.
And this is as much as I need
to move a mountain?
In theory, yes.
But it's up to Him.
He's the mover.
How could I get
bigger faith?
The list,
the ancient list.
For centuries, people believed
that if you do this list,
it'll make your
faith powerful.
This is what
you have to do.
"Feed the hungry,
shelter the homeless,
visit those in prison,
- clothe the naked. "
- Naked?
How is that
supposed to...
"Visit the sick,
bury the dead. "
Oh, just
one more thing.
In order to make this
list work for you,
I'm gonna add
one essential item.
"Befriend Hashimoto"?!
Are you crazy?
It's your choice,
Pepper.
What does that Jap
have to do with anything?
Everything.
Your faith won't work
if you have even the slightest
bit of hatred in you.
Fine.
I'll do it
if that's what it takes
to bring my dad back.
- Come again?
- Bring my dad back.
Yes, but only
if it's God's will.
Why wouldn't God want
to bring my dad back?
I don't know.
But if I get enough faith,
nothing's impossible, right?
Yeah.
What do you want?
I'm sorry about
the other day.
So, were you
nice to him?
Yeah. How can anyone
be friends with a Jap?
Take him a gift,
as a peace offering.
Hey, Jap.
Want a soda?
And all he did was
throw it in the trash.
Oh, I think
you'll be okay.
- Hang out with him.
- Hang out?
Yep.
Just get to know him.
Ollie, why are you getting me
involved in this?
I just don't see
how this helps anyone.
Yes, yes, he did,
but I don't even
drink soda.
Jeez.
Just tell the kid to stop.
Oh, no, he's back again.
Hey!
What are you doing
monkeying around my house?
I want to hang out.
Go hang out
somewhere else.
I meant with you.
Okay.
Let's "hang out. "
Come on, get in,
"Little Boy. "
Bad nicknames travel fast
in this town.
My family knows
where I am.
Especially London.
Okay,
let's hang out.
Go ahead,
I'll meet you inside.
No, no.
Okay.
What's he doing here?
Come.
What can I get you?
I'll have a chocolate
sundae with...
Hey, I ain't
talking to you, Nip.
What do you want,
Little Boy?
Two scoops of vanilla.
I haven't had
ice cream in years.
Why are you eating
my ice cream?
You can get
ice cream anytime.
Next time,
try chocolate.
- Now are we finished
hanging out? - Mm-hmm.
Then can I scratch you
from my list?
- What list?
- Father Oliver's "ancient list. "
No, Ollie.
You told the boy that
if he waves a magic wand,
he can bring his father back.
You don't believe that, do you?
Maybe.
Maybe not.
If it's God's will, yes.
He can do anything.
He could turn you into
a rabbit if He wanted to.
Have faith, Hashimoto.
You should try it.
Oh, not again.
I do have faith.
Faith in oneself.
Not in your imaginary
friend in the sky.
Let's hope this
little game of yours
doesn't mess
with the boy's mind.
Two weeks?
But what about the list?
I already finished
with the Jap.
Really?
We're friends now.
You continue
with Mr. Hashimoto
till I can't see the hate
in your eyes anymore.
Go and visit a prisoner.
You already know one.
I'll help you with
the list when I get back.
I promise.
Befriend that rat in order
to get dad back?
By doing this stupid list?
By befriending him, all you're
doing is betraying Dad.
Hey!
Where do you think
you're going, Little Boy?
Come on.
Jap lover!
You can drop me off here.
I don't have anyone
to help me with my list.
Hmm.
Okay.
First things first...
my name is not "Jap. "
It's Hashimoto.
Hmm?
All right, come in.
Okay, come.
Show me what you got.
Oh.
Where do we start?
"Visit those in prison. "
Why is this crossed out?
My brother.
Well... at least that schmuck
was good for something.
"Visit the sick. "
I can help you
with that one.
Okay, just wait
for me over here.
I'm here for my
monthly check-up.
Who's your friend?
- He's not my friend.
- Thank you.
Pepper.
Come on.
He's "not his friend. "
Hi.
I was just visiting.
You can keep it.
Thanks, kid.
"Shelter the homeless. "
Is that one-eared oaf
still working at the shop?
- Teacup?
- Hmm.
Yeah, he sleeps there.
Not quite a home, right?
What about London's
vacant bed?
Hey, they fit.
I've never worn
one of these before.
It feels... nice.
Then I guess you can
keep 'em, Teacup.
The next one...
"Clothe the naked. "
Hmm, "spider ladies. "
They "knit and bite" all day.
Shouldn't you
be somewhere,
playing with sticks
or something,
with your friends?
He has no friend.
You put these two...
I think the baby's
gonna like it.
Thank you.
With Hashimoto's help,
I'd finished the list
in no time.
And maybe he wasn't
so bad after all.
Things were looking up.
Good afternoon, Mrs. Busbee.
I took the liberty of stopping
by today because I...
I heard
about your husband
and...
get your hat off.
Mrs. Busbee, I want you
to know if you need anything,
you can count on me.
Thank you, Dr. Fox.
Yeah.
Boy, it smells good
in here.
Is that a casserole I smell?
It is.
Yeah, I thought
I could...
Would you like
to join us?
Yeah.
Seems Dr. Fox always
gets what he wants.
Dr. Fox?
This is great.
Thank you so much.
Here we go.
Mmm.
Emma...
Freddy and I
haven't eaten
like this since,
well, Clarice passed.
Um...
thank you for getting me
out of jail.
No trouble at all, son.
I would do anything
for your mother.
That's my dad's seat,
you know.
I can see why.
Best view in the house.
May I be excused?
Yes, you may.
Hey!
What are you doing...
I heard about your
stupid "magic list. "
And if you want it back,
you're gonna have to
get it from me.
But that was the list...
the ancient list.
I need that one.
If you need it so bad,
take it back from him.
How?
He's bigger than me.
Everybody's
bigger than me.
Okay, stand up.
Let's see
how small you are.
Hmm, right.
You're a very
small boy, indeed.
Toothpick arms,
cricket legs...
size of Masao Kume.
- Who's Masao...
- Kume.
- Samurai.
- What's that?
You don't know
what a samurai is?
Oh, these
are samurai...
Japanese warriors.
What one's Masao Kume?
Hmm. This
is Masao Kume.
- He doesn't look like a warrior.
- He wasn't.
Not yet.
Masao Kume was small.
Powerless.
Nothing but a servant.
But in every man's life,
there comes a day of truth.
And that day came
when the Mongols
invaded Japan.
Who are the Mongols?
They were bullies.
Samurai tried
to defend their land,
but Mongols had
"Bukha the Immense. "
The Mongols issued
a challenge.
If anyone could defeat
Bukha in battle,
they would leave Japan,
never to return.
Masao Kume believed
that nothing was more
powerful than the will.
The will to face
one's fear...
and to act.
Stand.
Now don't measure yourself
from here to the floor.
Measure yourself
from here to the sky.
That makes you
the tallest boy in town.
Hey, Freddy.
- Huh? - Look. Someone's
giving you the stink eye.
Looking for something...
Little Boy?
Maybe this.
It's a magic list, right?
Give it back.
Please?
You fat motherless pig!
Ugh!
Freddy, Freddy, Freddy!
This'll teach you
to never mess with me.
Freddy, Freddy, Freddy!
Freddy, Freddy,
Freddy, Freddy...
Freddy, Freddy!
I'm finishing you this time.
"Invite a friend over. "
Feed the hungry also means
inviting a friend to eat.
...box and whacked
him so hard.
I'll get it.
Good day, Mrs. Busbee.
I seem to have made
a mistake.
Would you wait there
a moment?
Yes.
I said for you
to invite a friend.
He is my friend.
There's been
no mistake.
Please come in,
Mr. Hashimoto.
Thank you,
Mrs. Busbee.
Do you have hot dogs
in Japan, Mr. Hashimoto?
No, Mrs. Busbee.
It's been 42 years
since I've been in Japan.
Seems like a lifetime ago.
And do you still have
relatives over there?
All I have left
of all my relatives
is a photo
of my two nephews
Takeshi and Koji.
They probably live
in my hometown still.
Haven't heard
from them since...
The war changed everything.
Yes, it has.
For everyone.
And did they send you away
to the camps?
Pepper, that is not the
kind of question you ask.
No, no, Mrs. Busbee,
it's okay.
It's simple.
I have the face
of the enemy.
Doesn't matter
if this is my home.
Doesn't matter if I love
this land, this country...
Mom, where's that
other set of keys?
That lamebrain
Teacup forgot...
- Maybe we should...
- Yes, I'll help you clean up.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
Sorry.
London?
London, what are you doing?
Put that down right now.
London, put it down
right now. Please?
London,
think about your dad.
Get out.
London, think about
what you're doing.
Please stop.
Stop.
Mrs. Busbee.
Pepper.
Get out now.
Or I'll shoot you
where you stand.
Get out!
A Jap will not eat
at my father's table.
This is all your fault!
Dad had to go to war
because you couldn't!
Listen to me. If I see you
hanging out with that rat,
- I will smack you in front
of everyone... - Enough!
You need to stop
this nonsense.
Stop what?
Stop an eight-year-old boy
from thinking that he can do
something to help his dad?
Tell me, London,
what is so wrong with that?
Nothing.
Except for when the day comes
to tell him the Japs killed his father.
Stop saying
your dad is dead.
- Mom, I'm just trying to be prepared.
- Oh, shut up.
Look at that.
You should go home now.
Is this man bothering you?
No.
He's my friend.
Look, I have no
business here with you.
All due respect,
I'm going my way.
With all due respect, you're not
going anywhere just yet.
Am I a joke to you?
Listen to me, if I see you
around my brother again,
I will put a bullet in your head.
Do you understand me?
That won't be needed. I think
"Mr. Buddha-head" here understands.
You got one week to pack your crap
and get your yellow hide out of here.
What, you don't
believe me?
You stay and find out.
Hey, listen to me.
You want to do something for Dad,
then you stop palling
around with this rat.
Stupid priest filling your head
with a bunch of fairy tales.
What if I can?
What if I can bring Dad back?
Dad back?
How?
How are you gonna bring
Dad back, you idiot?
Like... like,
with the mustard seed.
You can
"move a mountain. "
Fine.
You want to move a mountain?
There's one. Go ahead.
Move it.
Move it!
Move it for everyone!
You don't have to do it.
He's just trying
to humiliate you.
Hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey!
Not now.
No.
Calm down.
That's it.
Get clear!
Do you know when
Father Oliver's coming back?
- That's the little boy.
- Right.
- This was much more than just
an earthquake. - What was it?
It's a miracle.
Let people believe
what they want.
They need crap like this to believe that
there's something bigger than them.
Truth is, that earthquake would have
happened whether that boy was there or not.
I've been walking to work
for 35 years
and I'm telling you,
that mountain
was definitely...
more to the right.
Right?
Father Oliver?
What? What?
Yes, I heard about it on the...
No, a boy
moved a mountain.
He moved a what?
I figured it out!
Hashimoto!
Japan is practically
straight in front of us.
Now if you point to where
the sun touches the sea,
you'd be pointing
directly at Japan.
- Why the sudden interest?
- I need to end the war.
My dad can't come back
until it's over.
You mean doing this?
Yes.
All right, maybe it's time
I'm honest with you.
I don't believe that
you moved any mountain
or you had anything
to do with the earthquake.
You were there.
How could you say that?
I just don't believe
that anyone in the world
could do such a thing.
Then are you saying
I should stop?
I would say do what
makes sense for you.
It's just a loan,
for goodness' sake.
A loan from that Fox
has enough strings
- to start a puppet factory.
- And what do you suggest, then, huh?
Lose your father's shop?
We can pay him back
when your dad gets home.
I think Dr. Fox is counting
on Dad never coming home.
And his loan required you
to get all dolled up, huh?
Today is me and your dad's
wedding anniversary.
I'm sorry.
What's Little Boy doing?
I do believe men can
move mountains, Ollie.
With dynamite.
I believe that what
happened to the mountain
can't be reduced
to a game of chance.
Much of life is
a gamble, Ollie.
You're advising
a desperate child
who's ready to believe
anything that he is told.
So tell me, Ollie...
...what happens when
your imaginary friend
works in His
mysterious ways
and his father dies?
Then my "imaginary friend"
will also help him
through it.
Tell the kid to stop.
If he doesn't, could lose
faith in himself.
That's what you should
be worrying about.
- Said it in the papers.
- Little Boy.
That's Little Boy!
There he is!
Little Boy's here.
- You did it!
- You did it, son.
- Yes, you did.
- He has no idea.
Go on, go on,
read it to him.
Give me that.
Listen to this, Little Boy.
"The greatest power known
to man has been unleashed.
Yesterday
at 5:15 our time,
Hiroshima was destroyed by
the force of the atomic bomb,
codename... "
"Little Boy. "
- You did it.
I did it!
My daddy's coming home!
- You did it, Little Boy.
- My daddy's coming home.
I did it!
My daddy's coming home.
Did they say
when Dad's coming back?
I wish things
were that simple.
Colonel Bob said that
the bomb may not be good
for American prisoners.
What do you mean?
It means that the Japanese
may try to harm your dad
in revenge for the bomb.
It wiped out
an entire city.
Hello, Hashimoto.
I warned you.
But you dared stay.
And looking
on the bright side,
I ended up
doing you a favor.
It's imprudent
to keep all these traitorous
Japanese souvenirs.
Since we are at war
against Japan.
It was evil rats
just like you
who cowardly
murdered my son.
The yellow fella don't
take a hint, does he?
Doing this
won't bring back
your son.
Sam.
Sam, that's enough, Sam!
Let's get
outta here. Now!
Sam.
Sam, we can't... we can't just
leave him in there. He's gonna die.
If we're caught here and he dies,
we rot in jail. Do you understand me?
Get in the truck.
Get in the truck now!
Okay, you wanna play the hero?
That's your choice.
But you better be man enough to face
the consequences on your own.
How is he?
His heart is very weak.
But he's gonna be
okay, right?
I don't know.
You have to let one die.
Make your choice.
Hashimoto.
Hashimoto...?
Pepper.
Nurse!
- Get the doctor.
- Dr. Foley!
- I need oxygen.
- Right away.
Mr. Hashimoto, can you hear me?
Can you hear me?
He's stopped breathing.
Please don't die.
You're free.
The Jap dropped the charges.
Says you saved his life.
Whatever that means.
Ma'am.
It's time.
We were told my father was laid
to rest in the Philippines.
My mother still chose to have
a memorial for him back home.
Let us commit James L. Busbee's
body to the ground,
earth to earth,
ashes to ashes,
dust to dust,
in the sure
and certain hope
of the resurrection
to eternal life.
In the name of the Father
and of the Son
and of the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
You're my only partner.
Do you mind if I sit here?
You know, I...
never got to say
goodbye to my wife.
By the time I got
to the hospital,
she was already
in a coma.
She died
the next morning.
I think it was stupid
of me to believe
that a midget like me
could bring my dad back
with some stupid list.
It was not stupid.
It takes courage
to believe.
Your father would be
more than proud of you.
All the love you have for him
was contained in that list.
I did this for you.
- 39 inches.
- Same as before.
I'm afraid I still
don't have a diagnosis
for his irregular
development,
but I do have
some theories.
Maybe I could come over
the house later
and we could discuss them.
Perhaps tonight?
I really appreciate the help
you've given us.
I really do,
but right now,
my family
needs some time alone.
Maybe after some time...
You're a good man, Dr. Fox.
But I will always be
Mrs. James Busbee.
Come on.
- I need more bandages!
- What's the name on this one?
- I got him, I got him.
- Get that on his head!
"James L. Busbee...
39627771. "
You did it, you little runt.
You did it.
London!
Father Oliver said God
was responsible
for bringing
my dad back.
Hashimoto said it was
my father's will to live.
He survived an extremely
severe trauma.
Me?
Oh, I was holding on
to my mustard seed...
because the journey
was not over yet.
Partner...?
I got the boots
you really wanted.
It's me, partner.
Partner.
Subtitle:
sync, fix: titler