Previously on AMC's
The Walking Dead...
I don't cry any more, Daryl.
Are you okay?
Just tired of losing people, so?
I'm low on the ammo.
Run by the bus.
I'll cover you.
Beth!
Where is Beth?
I'm just trying to find the kids,
to get them on the bus.
We gotta go back.
We gotta go.
We aren't the only survivors.
We can't be.
Come on.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
I need a drink.
No, I mean a real drink.
As in alcohol.
I've never had one.
'Cause of my dad.
But he's not exactly
around anymore, so...
I thought we could
go find some.
Okay.
Well, enjoy your snake jerky.
Jerk.
I think we made it a way.
I'm pretty sure we got to go
that way to find the booze.
What the hell?
You brought me back.
I'm not staying
in this suck-ass camp.
Hey!
You had your fun.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Do you feel anything?
Yeah, you think
everything's screwed.
I guess that's a feeling.
So you want to spend
the rest of our lives
staring into a fire
and eating mud snakes?
Screw that.
We might as well do something.
I can take care of myself
and I'm gonna get a damn drink.
Golfers like to
booze it up, right?
Come on.
Might be people inside.
Why are you keeping
all that stuff?
Come on.
Thanks for the help.
You said you could
take care of yourself.
You did.
_
Help me take her down.
It don't matter.
She's dead.
It does matter.
Here.
Okay.
Move.
We made it.
I know you think
this is stupid.
And it probably is.
But I don't care.
All I wanted to do today
was lay down and cry,
but we don't get to do that.
So beat up on walkers if
that makes you feel better.
I need to do this.
Did you have to
break the glass?
No.
You have your drink yet?
But I found this.
Peach schnapps.
- Is it good?
- No.
Well, it's the only thing left.
Who needs a glass?
Ain't gonna have
your first drink
be no damned peach schnapps.
Come on.
A motorcycle mechanic.
- Huh?
- That's my guess.
For what you were doing
before the turn.
Did Zack ever guess that one?
It don't matter.
Hasn't mattered
for a long time.
It's just what
people talk about,
you know, to feel normal.
Yeah, well, that never
felt normal to me.
Found this place with Michonne.
I was expecting a liquor store.
No, this is better.
What's that?
Moonshine.
Come on.
All right.
That's a real
first drink right there.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
It's just...
my dad always said bad moonshine
can make you go blind.
Ain't nothing worth seeing
out there anymore anyway.
That's the most disgusting
thing I've ever tasted.
Second round's better.
Slow down.
- This one's for you.
- No, I'm good.
- Why?
- Someone's got to keep watch.
So, what, you're like
my chaperone now?
Just drink lots of water.
Yes, Mr. Dixon.
Who'd go into a store
and walk out with this?
My dad, that's who.
Oh, he's a dumbass.
He'd set those up
on top of the TV set,
use them as target practice.
He shot things
inside your house?
It was just a bunch
of junk anyway.
That's how I knew
what this place was.
That shed out there, my dad
had a place just like this.
You got your Dumpster chair.
That's for sitting in and your
drawers all summer drinking.
Got your fancy buckets.
That's for spitting chaw in
after your old lady
tells you to stop smoking.
You got your internet.
- It's just one of 'em.
- Should we get it?
If he keeps making
too much noise, yeah.
Well, if we're gonna
be trapped again,
we might as well
make the best of it.
Unless you're too busy
chaperoning, Mr. Dixon.
Hell, might as well
make the best of it.
Home, sweet home.
So first I say something
I've never done
and if you have done it,
you drink,
and if you haven't, I drink.
Then we switch.
You really don't
know this game?
I never needed a game
to get lit before.
Wait, are we starting?
- How do you know this game?
- My friends played.
I watched.
Okay, I'll start.
I've never shot a crossbow.
So now you drink.
Ain't much of a game.
That was a warm-up.
Now you go.
I don't know.
Just say the first thing
that pops into your head.
I've never been out of Georgia.
Really?
Okay, good one.
I've never...
been drunk and did
something I regretted.
I've done a lot of things.
Your turn.
I've never been on vacation.
What about camping?
No, that was just something
I had to learn to hunt.
Your dad teach you?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
I've never...
been in jail.
I mean, as a prisoner.
Is that what you think of me?
I didn't mean anything serious.
I just thought, you know,
like the drunk tank.
Even my dad got locked up
for that back in the day.
- Drink up.
- Wait.
Prison guard.
Were you a prison guard before?
No.
It's your turn again.
I'm gonna take a piss.
You have to be quiet.
Can't hear you!
I'm taking a piss!
Daryl, don't talk so loud.
What, are you my chaperone now?
Oh, wait.
It's my turn, right?
I've never--
never eaten frozen yogurt.
Never had a pet pony.
Never got nothing
from Santa Claus.
Never relied on anyone
for protection before.
Hell, I don't think I've ever
relied on anyone for anything.
- Daryl.
- Never sung out in front of a big group
out in public
like everything was fun.
Like everything was a big game.
I sure as hell never cut my
wrists looking for attention.
Sounds like our friend out there is
trying to call all of his buddies.
- Daryl, just shut up.
- Hey, you never shot a crossbow before?
I'm gonna teach you right now.
Come on.
It's gonna be fun.
We should stay inside.
Daryl, cut it out!
- Daryl!
- Dumbass.
Come here, dumbass.
- Daryl.
- You want to shoot?
- I don't know how.
- Oh, it's easy.
Come here.
Right corner.
Let's practice later.
- Come on, it's fun.
- Just stop it.
- Daryl!
- Come here.
- Eight ball.
- Just kill it!
Come here, Greene.
Let's pull these out.
Get a little more
target practice.
What the hell you do that for?
I was having fun.
No, you were being a jackass.
- If anyone found my dad--
- Don't.
That ain't remotely the same.
Killing them is not
supposed to be fun.
What do you want
from me, girl, huh?
I want to you stop acting like you
don't give a crap about anything.
Like nothing
we went through matters.
Like none of the people we
lost meant anything to you.
It's bullshit!
- Is that what you think?
- That's what I know.
You don't know nothing.
I know you look at me and you
just see another dead girl.
I'm not Michonne. I'm not Carol.
I'm not Maggie.
I've survived
and you don't get it
'cause I'm not
like you or them.
But I made it and you don't
get to treat me like crap
just because you're afraid.
I ain't afraid of nothing.
I remember.
When that little girl
came out of the barn
after my mom.
You were like me.
And now God forbid
you ever let anybody
get too close.
Too close, huh?
You know all about that.
You lost two boyfriends,
you can't even shed a tear.
Your whole family's gone, all you can
do is just go out looking for hooch
like some dumb college bitch.
Screw you.
You don't get it.
No, you don't get it!
- Everyone we know is dead!
- You don't know that!
Might as well be, 'cause you
ain't never gonna see 'em again.
Rick. You ain't never
gonna see Maggie again.
- Daryl, just stop.
- No!
The Governor rolled
right up to our gates.
Maybe if I wouldn't
have stopped looking.
Maybe 'cause I gave up.
That's on me.
- Daryl.
- No--
And your dad.
Maybe-- maybe I could
have done something.
I get why my dad
stopped drinking.
You feel sick?
Nope.
I wish I could feel
like this all the time.
That's bad.
Hmm.
You're lucky
you're a happy drunk.
Yeah, I'm lucky.
Some people can be
real jerks when they drink.
Yeah, I'm a dick
when I'm drunk.
Merle had this dealer.
This janky little white guy.
A tweaker.
One day we were
over at his house
watching TV.
Wasn't even noon yet
and we were all wasted.
Merle was high.
We were watching this show
and Merle was talking
all this dumb stuff about it.
And he wouldn't let up.
Merle never could.
Turns out
it was the tweaker's
kids' favorite show.
And he never sees his kids,
so he felt guilty
about it or something.
So he punches
Merle in the face.
So I started hitting
the tweaker, like, hard.
As hard as I can.
Then he pulls a gun,
sticks it right here.
He says, "I'm gonna
kill you, bitch."
So Merle pulls his gun on him.
Everyone's yelling.
I'm yelling.
I thought I was dead.
Over a dumb cartoon
about a talking dog.
How'd you get out of it?
The tweaker punched me
in the gut.
I puked.
They both started laughing
and forgot all about it.
You want to know
what I was before all this?
I was just drifting
around with Merle...
doing whatever he said we
were gonna be doing that day.
I was nobody.
Nothing.
Some redneck asshole
and an even bigger
asshole for a brother.
You miss him, don't you?
I miss Maggie.
I miss her bossing me around.
I miss my big brother Shawn.
He was so annoying
and overprotective.
And my dad.
I thought--
I hoped he'd just live the rest
of his life in peace, you know?
I thought Maggie and Glenn
would have a baby.
And he'd get to be a grandpa.
And we'd have birthdays
and holidays
and summer picnics.
And he'd get really old.
And it'd happen,
but it'd be quiet.
It'd be okay.
He'd be surrounded
by people he loved.
That's how unbelievably
stupid I am.
That's how
it was supposed to be.
I wish I could just...
change.
You did.
Not enough.
Not like you.
It's like you were made
for how things are now.
I'm just used to it,
things being ugly.
Growing up
in a place like this.
Well, you got away from it.
- I didn't.
- You did.
Maybe you got to keep on
reminding me sometimes.
No.
You can't depend on anybody
for anything, right?
- I'll be gone someday.
- Stop.
I will.
You're gonna be
the last man standing.
You are.
You're gonna miss me so bad
when I'm gone, Daryl Dixon.
You ain't a happy drunk at all.
Yeah, I'm happy.
I'm just not blind.
You got to stay who you are,
not who you were.
Places like this,
you have to put it away.
What if you can't?
You have to.
Or it kills you.
Here.
We should go inside.
We should burn it down.
We're gonna need more booze.
♪ there's bound to be a ghost ♪
♪ at the back of your closet ♪
♪ no matter where you live ♪
♪ there'll always
be a few things ♪
♪ maybe several things ♪
♪ that you're gonna find
really difficult to forgive... ♪
- You wanna?
- Hell, yeah.
♪ there's gonna come a day ♪
♪ when you feel better ♪
♪ your eyes are free and easy ♪
♪ on that day ♪
♪ and float from branch
to branch ♪
♪ lighter than the air ♪
♪ just when that day
is coming ♪
♪ who can say?
who can say? ♪
♪ our mother has been absent ♪
♪ ever since we founded Rome ♪
♪ but there's gonna
be a party ♪
♪ when the wolf comes home ♪
♪ I'm gonna get myself
in fighting trim ♪
♪ scope out every angle
of unfair advantage ♪
♪ I'm gonna bribe
the officials ♪
♪ I'm gonna kill
all the judges ♪
♪ it's gonna take
you people years ♪
♪ to recover
from all of the damage ♪
♪ our mother has been absent ♪
♪ ever since we founded Rome ♪
♪ but there's
gonna be a party ♪
♪ when the wolf comes home ♪
♪ Oh! ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com